## **Broc Atkinson**

## atkinsonbg@gmail.com

Bootcamp Graduate in MERN full stack development, ready to learn.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Bodie Enger Law, — Paralegal

August 2017 - PRESENT

- Opposing parties investigation
- Post judgment enforcement
- Legal research and review
- Document drafting
- Settlement negotiation

# HindmanSanchez now Altitude Community Law, — *Paralegal*

November 2011 - August 2017

- Tasked with working the largest active caseload of the department
- Foreclosures and Bankruptcy analysis
- Calculation of amounts due
- Heavy client and general public contact
- Skip trace and evaluate credit reports

#### **Robert Hopp Law Firm**, — *Paralegal*

January 2010 - November 2011

- Public Trustee foreclosure monitoring and sales bid preparation
- Calculate Payoff amounts
- Eviction process file intake to eviction in multiple states
- Reorganization and training of sales Department
- Legal document drafting

## **PROJECTS**

**Group project** — This was a group project where we decided on a storefront website.

https://shrouded-crag-31196.herokuapp.com/

#### **About**

When you take in life and professional experience, my skill set is very unique.
Hospitality,luxury automotive, legal now completing a full stack web development course using the MERN stack. With a diverse background and team player mentality, I am easily added into a team without disrupting the chemistry or culture.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Denver University, — Full stack Web development

May 2019 - December 2019
6 month bootcamp covering the basics into the MERN stack. Below is the link to my last project where I worked primarily on the backend.

## Adams State, — Paralegal Certificate

December 2009